{
    "subject": "resource/Emmanuel_Le_Roy_Ladurie",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/surname",
    "object": "Le Roy Ladurie",
    "human_readable": "The surname of Emmanuel Le Roy Ladurie is Le Roy Ladurie.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9875079989433289,
            "question": "What is the surname of Emmanuel Le Roy Ladurie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9785693883895874,
            "question": "Is there a famous person with the same surname as Emmanuel Le Roy Ladurie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.933210551738739,
            "question": "What is the origin of the surname 'Le Roy Ladurie'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9226030707359314,
            "question": "Is 'Le Roy Ladurie' a common surname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8773520588874817,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with Emmanuel Le Roy Ladurie's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8241698741912842,
            "question": "Could you tell me more about Emmanuel Le Roy Ladurie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8166214227676392,
            "question": "How does the surname 'Le Roy Ladurie' compare to other French surnames?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6780471205711365,
            "question": "What field of study is Emmanuel Le Roy Ladurie known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6554753184318542,
            "question": "Has Emmanuel Le Roy Ladurie published any notable works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6028202176094055,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of surnames like 'Le Roy Ladurie'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The surname of Emmanuel Le Roy Ladurie is Le Roy Ladurie.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5534_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Emmanuel Le Roy Ladurie published any notable works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5534_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field of study is Emmanuel Le Roy Ladurie known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5534_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the surname 'Le Roy Ladurie' compare to other French surnames?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5534_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5534_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5534_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5534_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5534_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5534_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5534_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5534_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5534_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5534_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5534_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the context information, the surname of Emmanuel Le Roy Ladurie is actually de Roy Laduries before dropping the aristocratic de from their surname at the time of the French Revolution."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Emmanuel Le Roy Ladurie, including his full name and the fact that \"Le Roy Ladurie\" is part of his surname."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The surname of Emmanuel Le Roy Ladurie's family was originally \"de Roy Laduries\", not just \"Le Roy Ladurie\".",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}